1) What is the purpose of a splitter? Can it be used to join wires?
     Answer
	A spliter creates a connecting link between a multi-bit value and several separate subsets of those bits. 
	As a connecting link, it can split a multi-bit value into component parts as its name shows
	or it can combine component parts into a multi-bit value.
	In addition, it can also do both way at once.

2) Why are tunnels useful?
     Answer
	It can transmit signals without using wires.
	Therefore when points far apart in a circuit are needed to connect, it will be helpful.
	Because it will make the circuit clean.

3) What is the output of your circuit when you give it an input of 010? How about an input of 100?
     Answer
	When I gave it an input of 010, the circuit still showed 0 as an output value.
	When I gave it an input of 100, the circuit showed 1 as an output value.